It's Google, Apple. Who do you think
makes the greatest products of the two?
Data scientist is the sexiest job of the
21st century. As I've grown older, I've
kind of started giving more weight to
intuition. Like when I was uh in data
science, we were always trying to arrest
people for using intuition. Like you
have to use data, you have to be data
informed, data driven. But I think
there's a lot of value in intuition as
well.
>> What have you observed about human
behavior? Because people can't lie on
chain. Oh yeah, there's a lot. Most
people lose money on meme coins and
there's a few people that make a lot of
money. The ones that make the most money
are actually [music] the memecoin
trading platforms. It's pretty hard
actually to compete the market or to
beat [music] the smartest money. If you
know you're being observed, maybe you
can use that to your benefit. That's
part of the game. Sometimes you see this
like sensationalist post of like, hey,
so and so went super long on this and
whatever, but in reality it might have
been hedged. So you have to be a little
bit careful. This is [music] me becoming
a little bit like data scientist. The
bull market has been over for retail for
a long time. Probably since January
>> and people are just talking about it
now.
>> You have to skate where the puck is
going instead of just thinking this is
what the world looks like today.
>> I want your opinion on Ethereum now.
>> You could imagine a world where like no
one uses Ethereum. But
>> we are in Dubai with one of the smartest
guy in crypto, Alex from Nansen. How are
you?
>> I'm doing great, Bonnie. How are you
>> with that shirt? I can't really tell.
You're an all numbers guy, [laughter]
>> right?
>> I don't know if I'm an all numbers guy,
but numbers guy.
>> But you are also a data scientist.
>> That's right. Yes. My background is
actually in AI. I like to say that I was
in AI before it was cool.
>> Mhm.
>> And uh I worked as a management
consultant for a few years and then I
was a data scientist and a data science
manager uh for a while. And so you know
maybe that uh ages me or dates me
somewhat. Um, but when I graduated
actually there was a front page article
I think on the economist that said data
scientist is the sexiest job of the 21st
century. So I had to go into data
science.
>> They were right. That that was how long
ago?
>> Uh this was 2009 2010.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Oh, I have a question about data
scientists. So I heard this argument
that you know in the future the truth is
the numbers. Like we listen to AI and
they give us the correct answer.
>> Yeah.
>> So that sort of replace
I don't know if you're ready for this
religion.
>> Oh wow. That's
>> um the truth
>> of the world.
>> I mean in some ways as I've grown older
I've kind of started giving more weight
to intuition.
>> Like when I was uh in data science we
were always trying to kind of arrest
people for using intuition. Like you
have to use data you have to be data
informed data driven. Um, but I think
there's a lot of value in intuition as
well.
>> And so I think the magic is to like
combine the two.
>> So obviously the way I run the company
Nson is quite data informed
>> but there's also a lot of use of
intuition as well and taste and
judgment. When you think about building
great products for example I think take
two companies Google
>> Apple.
>> Who do you think makes the greatest
products of the two?
>> Google. Okay. Interesting. I think it's
Apple.
>> Okay.
>> But Google products are also very good.
But Google products are much more I
think data oriented in their product
development. Lots of AB testing. Let's
change this a little bit and if the
results are statistically significant,
we'll switch the button from like green
to blue or something like that.
>> Whereas Apple is much more demo driven.
At least when Jobs was leading Apple,
very demo-driven, very um dog fooding
oriented, although I I don't think they
like the term dog fooding at Apple, but
basically using your own products
>> and essentially trying to use great
taste and judgment and how you design
products. And so, in a way, I think the
older I've gotten, the more I'm leaning
into like taste, judgment, um, and
intuition for product development. But I
think when it comes to trading to kind
of take it back to crypto and investing,
it is generally probably a good idea to
use data
>> and to look at the numbers and not only
rely on your own intuitions for most
people at least.
>> You have analyzed I don't know billions
of transactions or at least millions.
>> I think tens of billions of transactions
like our platform
>> that is a lot. And what have you
observed about human behavior because
people can't lie on chain.
>> Yeah. old.
>> Yeah, there's a lot. You could probably
write a book about that. Um, I mean,
there's there's a few different things.
Last time I was in Dubai, actually, one
thing I was talking about is how uh most
people lose money on meme coins.
>> Uh, and there's a few people that make a
lot of money and the the ones that make
the most money are actually the memecoin
trading platforms,
>> right? people are quite optimistic I
guess like one nice way to put it about
their own abilities to trade onchain but
in reality
it's pretty hard actually to out compete
the market or to beat the smartest money
and so one thing we do a lot at nonsen
is to measure you know what is smart
money
>> yeah what do they do
>> and so smart money investors I mean the
way we sort of define it loosely is that
these are addresses that have really
high P&L, right? So, they're
consistently very good at trading or
investing. And sometimes you can be
smart money, but then you can lose your
status and become we even labeled them
in the in that platform as former smart
money, which is kind of funny. But if I
go back to say like 202,
uh there were a lot of people that
people considered smart money. Think of
three arrows for example, that ended up
being not so smart money. Uh and so over
the over the years, I think one thing
we've learned is actually pay less
attention to the names and just look at
the behavior they have, right? So just
because you have a famous fund doesn't
mean that you're going to be really
successful in investing. Actually, we
have a lot of smart money addresses that
we've tagged. We have no idea who they
are
>> because they're just some person in
their, I don't know, bedroom trading and
they're doing super well, but no one
knows who they are. And there's a bunch
of those in.
>> Yeah. I want to know. So smart money, I
used to think it is just people that
trade very smart and like very
strategically, but in terms of what you
just described, being famous is also
smart money.
>> It used Yeah, it used to be uh part of
the definition, but we've actually
removed that.
>> So now it's all behavior. We discovered
that the names don't actually reflect
that much what whether people are going
to be successful at trading. And so we
eliminated that component and now you
have to earn the smart money status
based on your own onchain trading um
performance. So, if you're really good
at trading on hyperlid, you could become
a smart pers trader,
>> which is kind of a subcategory of uh
smart money. If you're good at, you
know, trading meme coins, um even
flipping NFTts, yield farming, there's a
bunch of different ways you can become
smart money. But the way I think about
it is that you have probably hundreds of
millions of addresses that you could be
looking at on chain. And so what we try
to do is surface the signal and
highlight the few thousand addresses
that are actually smart and you want to
follow what they're doing.
>> Do you personally follow anything?
>> I do follow what's happening on chain.
Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Uh increasingly I'm using our mobile app
called Nson AI
>> because I just find it's more
convenient. Uh and it's an agentic user
experience. I can just talk to it. I
don't have to like look at all the
dashboards and like oh you know slice
the data filter it you know sort uh I
can just go into the app and then ask it
like
>> which tokens are smart money buying
today
>> and then it tells me and then I can be
like who are the top traders on Hyperlid
in the last seven days and it'll tell me
and you know oh I've heard about I don't
know X42
tokens what are they and what are the
top tokens and then it tells me and Soon
you're going to be able to say, "Okay,
cool. Number two there looks
interesting." Put $100 into it and you
can execute trades directly in an
integrated user experience within the
app.
>> Can I say I want to stop loss of 20%.
>> That's a good question. Not in the first
version. Okay.
>> But you will be able to do that. Yeah.
For now, it's only spot swaps. So like
market orders on chain with the spot
trading.
>> I love that. And people are talking
about strategies like if you could in
traditional finance if you could follow
Warren Buffett's trade.
>> Yeah.
>> Then you would be very wealthy. And
people are trying to copy that onchain.
But I have a question. So remember
people are talking about this address on
hyperlquid that could be Trump's son.
>> Could be.
>> And then later on prove that it is not.
But anyway, that address made a lot of
money. But
>> when people start following all of a
sudden he lost everything.
>> Maybe he knew that people were
following.
>> So see like like so how do you use this
onchain data to
>> Yeah. Yeah. So I think you bring up a
very good point which is that you
shouldn't just naively
>> copy trade
>> what people do onchain because there's
many kind of nuances and qualifiers to
all this. One thing is that they could
be hedging, right? So you could have
other addresses,
>> right?
>> Another thing is that you could be
hedging even on a centralized exchange.
So sometimes you see this like
sensationalist posts of like, hey, so
and so, you know, went super long on
this and whatever, but in reality it
might have been hedged, right? So you
have to be a little bit careful. I treat
it as mostly an indicator that at least
they're trading it.
>> Uh, and that is enough for me to at
least look at it,
>> right? It doesn't mean necessarily that
they are actually long, truly long, like
if you had factored in all the addresses
and the centralized exchange, all the
stuff. So that's one thing. The other
thing is that if you know you're being
observed, maybe you can use that to your
benefit. That's part of the game though
and to me it makes it more interesting
in a way, right? It's like some people
of course have reservations about the
transparency of the blockchain and how
it relates to privacy for example, but
to me it's like don't hate the player,
hate the chain, right? you just have to
uh acknowledge that this is how
blockchains work and you might as well
lean into it and then just [snorts]
create strategies to either get around
that or like figure out how to use that
to your advantage. But I think yeah it
can be a little bit risky just naively
taking at face value here's what this
one address is doing and then copy
trading it.
>> If you are talking to a person that's
pretty new to crypto and they want to do
this tracking on chain type of thing.
What would you suggest them to do like
maybe three things that they have to
either look at or pay attention?
>> Well, the first one is go and see what
smart money is doing. So, I think my
framework is generally like there's
discovery and then there's due
diligence, right? Discovery means I just
want to figure out which tokens I should
be looking at in the first place,
>> right?
>> And so, smart money is a great indicator
of that. Like here are tokens that smart
money has at least been engaging with
somehow,
>> right? So I I look at that first. Then
for due diligence, you can look at who
actually owns the tokens, right? And
this sounds trivial, but in order to
have a good understanding of that, you
need to have labeled addresses. If I
show you a cap table of a token and it
says, you know, a bunch of addresses, it
doesn't tell you much. But if it's like
this is Dragonfly, this is A6 andZ, this
is Paradigm, this is, you know, Defiance
Capital, and here's the liquidity on all
the exchanges. Binance holds this much,
Coinbase, Kraken, OKX, whatever, you
just get a a much richer understanding
of the token. So, at the due diligence
step, I think understanding the supply
and how it's where the tokens are
sitting literally in different entities
and different addresses. And then
probably the third thing I would do is
set up smart alerts, which is a feature
we have. You can actually do it with our
mobile just agentically. You can tell it
like, "Hey, I want an alert every time,
you know, u Defiance Capital makes a
$100,000 transaction or more."
Literally, just say that to the agent
and it'll set up the alert for you and
you get notifications uh anytime that
happens. So, probably those three
things.
>> I want to know one of your alerts.
>> One of my one
>> alerts, like one actual one that you
have on right now.
>> I mean, I have a I have a lot actually.
Um, well, there was an exchange that got
uh hacked, I think last week, a Korean
exchange. Um, so I set up alerts on
their wallets to see if you know there
was a lot of outflow from those wallets.
So that's kind of like a overall like
market panic type of alert. Like if
suddenly there's
>> $500 million in some tokens coming out,
that's probably not a great sign.
>> Uh, so that's one I have active. I have
some Pudgy Penguins related alerts. My
my shoes here have some beautiful
penguins.
>> Wow.
>> And so so I have some uh Pangu alerts.
>> Nice.
>> And uh I have alerts on my own wallets
too because it makes me
>> feel good because if suddenly someone
>> Well, that's smart.
>> Compromised wallet like I would know
very quickly.
>> That is very smart. All the players in
crypto used to be just Binance and all
the exchanges but now we have a lot of
institutions now
>> and how does that affect onchain inflows
outflows?
>> It's been a very strange year because um
if you look at retail activity it's been
pretty poor without sounding judgmental
like the low end of the retail like
smaller wallets maybe lower net worth uh
retail has been largely absent since
January. So if you look at websites like
coin gecko, coin market cap, deck
screener and so on, they're down like 50
to 80% in traffic. Clearly
uh they're not the ones holding up the
market and market's been like a little
bit up and down. Um but it seems like a
lot of the flows are actually
institutionally driven especially for
Bitcoin, ETH, Salana and so on. um the
major L1's and so when you think about
institutions I think you can separate
between like cryptonative institutions
like market makers like Wintermute or
large funds like ACNC and then like the
trady wall street institutions and I
think now you're kind of getting the
rails in place like ETFs
DATs which are kind of unwinding to some
extent uh in place so I think like the
Vanguard um uh announcement I think one
or two days ago was pretty bullish in
that sense because it creates new
inroads for capital into crypto. So
yeah, it's kind of a mixed picture. I
think the the the lower-end cryptonative
retail has not had a great have not had
a great year, but then there's kind of a
almost like passing on the baton to a
different cohort like high capital, high
netw worth, more institutional type
investors. But yeah, I think our view is
that every asset is going to come on
chain eventually and so we just focus on
building a really great product for
onchain and the belief is that retail
institutions everyone is going to come
on chain and
Trading View Trading View.
Fore
two questions there. One for people that
are not familiar with what happened to
Vanguard. Maybe elaborate a little bit
on that. I think basically they just
announced that you can now trade crypto
ETFs on their platforms or yeah their
products
>> and then crypto was up a little bit. I
don't know if it's because of this.
>> I don't know if it's flows or sentiment
a bit of both. I'm not sure actually.
But yeah.
>> And the second question is since you
mentioned all these like big players the
like the big institutions.
>> Uh how do we even tell if the bull
market is ending if we don't know if
retails are excited or not? That's why I
think you could argue that the bull
market has been over for retail for a
long time.
>> How long a year?
>> Uh probably since January for for retail
>> and people are just talking about it
now.
>> But I think that's the thing like when
you this is me becoming a little bit
like data scientist again. But if you
have like multiple different
distributions that you add up it can
create like actually a pretty flat
picture but then you know one had a peak
here and another one had a peak there.
So I think I think actually you could
argue that we've been in a retail bare
market for like many months if not like
almost a full year.
>> Um but I think like I said a lot of it
is being held up by new sources of
capital. You're even seeing it to some
extent in like the M&A sector of crypto
where large companies that have access
to capital are getting the capital and
then they're buying smaller players that
are like out of capital or are not doing
that great or they frankly just want to
be part of like a bigger platform. And
so a few examples that come to mind,
these are great products. So they were
not struggling at all, but think of like
Privy being acquired by Stripe, Dynamic
being acquired by Fireblocks, and then
there's a bunch of other ones. We're not
a huge player, but we bought a staking
provider a year ago, which has been
fantastic for us. We've grown that
business many times over just in one
year. When we acquired that staking
company, they had $60 million staked
with their validators that we run for
different networks. and we basically
crossed $2 billion asset stake in less
than 8 months after acquiring them. So
sometimes it just makes sense to be a
smaller player part of a bigger
platform. The capital structure now
seems to support this as well where like
big players might have access to
capital. They can use that to actually
scoop up some of these smaller companies
and make them part of their offering.
>> When you make decisions, are you looking
at the numbers and predicting what's
going to happen next or are we only
talking about now? what is happening?
>> It depends on what decisions you're
making. You know, I think for product
decisions largely, at least product
vision and product strategy, I really
try to think long term
>> and uh it's actually based on some very
simple beliefs that I have. One is that
every asset is going to be tokenized,
which means that billions of people are
going to be owners. And so essentially
it's a good idea to build for onchain
because that's where everyone is going
to come anyway. So people think why
don't you integrate more with like
centralized exchanges? Why don't you add
like stock trading or like more trady
oriented things and I'm not really
interested because if we just build for
onchain all of those things are just
going to come on chain and then we get
it for free. So a good example is
tokenized stocks
because we are so religiously focused on
onchain tokenized stocks are happening
right that means stocks are coming on
chain either backed or uh synthetic now
you can analyze those with nonsen and
you can potentially trade them in the
future right the synthetic stocks um
that are tokenized and so that's an
example of like why why integrate with
tradfi and like legacy financial rails
if you can just build directly for
onchain and the world is going to move
on chain anyway. So that's how I think
about the product vision and product
strategy. But then there's a bunch of
other things that are more tactical
whether it's you know chain which chains
do you bet on that's an
>> in yeah that's one that's one we're
going to talk about later but let me
interrupt you there but how does that
>> affect well why is that your approach
different from let's say integrating
with an exchange because if the endgame
is everything goes on chain then
>> exchanges are part of the big picture.
Yeah, but the exchanges are going to
have to come on chain, so they're going
to have to connect with So, for example,
I know we're at Binance Blockchain Week,
but does it make sense for Nelson to
have like portfolio tracking of your
holdings on Binance, the centralized
exchange? You could argue right now it
makes sense, but in 2030, I don't think
it makes sense because it's all going to
be on chain.
>> Okay?
>> And they're very well positioned with
BNB chain, just to be clear, right? Um,
but so like you have to skate where the
puck is going instead of just thinking
this is what the world looks like today.
An interesting one is like which chains
to support and that's that's harder
because it's almost like you're almost
doing a form of like venture investing
but you're not investing capital
although sometimes you do that as well.
You're investing your company's time and
resources. And so is this a chain that
we want to spend a lot of time
integrating into our platform or should
we just ignore it? It's just hot right
now, but in six months it's going to be
dead.
>> It's hard. Yeah, you look at a bunch of
different factors, right? Are they well
capitalized? Does the technology make
sense? Do you believe in the team?
Actually is very similar things as what
you would look at as an investor. Can it
play a role in 2030, 2040? When you
imagine what the future of finance is
going to look like, that's kind of what
you have to think. So, I'll give some
examples like Salana crushing it. Uh we
actually integrated it in 2022 quite
early but admittedly our integration was
a little bit bad and slow because it's a
chain with lots of activity. So we had
to like reintegrated later but we've
consistently double down on Salana in
terms of like integrations what we
support data features. We run a
validator for Salana and we have a fun
announcement in January with Salana that
I'm looking forward to. Uh we're going
to have trading on Salana. So anyway,
like Son is a good example. B&B chain is
another good example, right? Has lots of
um genuine activity, DEX volume, active
addresses, transactions, some TVL, not
as much as Ethereum. And so you can look
at these metrics. Another interesting
one, maybe a controversial one, is Tron,
right?
>> I I use Tron.
>> Yeah, that's the thing. Like I think
people some people don't realize how
much Tron is used actually. It has tons
of stable coins. it actually generates
tons of revenues and so that's
definitely one of the kind of top
handful of chains. Then you have
Hyperlquid
>> which people use a lot for per trading.
It's a fantastic product kind of end to
end. Uh we run the largest hyperlquid
validator besides the foundation and we
have great support for hyperlquid
analytics and so you can imagine a world
where like all these chains live side by
side they play their own role.
>> I want your opinion on Ethereum. Now
people are disappointed.
They were happy for a few months and
then they they were sad again. So
>> I don't know. It's tricky. Clearly you
have some network effects and very very
smart people building in the Ethereum
ecosystem and investing in the Ethereum
ecosystem. Uh I don't think it's going
away anytime soon. Uh I guess my fear
would be that it's kind of my analogy is
like Netscape was kind of the first
browser that was very successful. They
developed JavaScript and so the analogy
would be like Ethereum and EVM.
Actually the main the main thing that
lives on after Netscape is JavaScript
which all the other browsers took but
built better browsers with than
Netscape. And so no one uses Netscape
now but everyone uses JavaScript. All
the browsers use JavaScript. You could
imagine a world, I'm not saying it's
going to happen, you could imagine a
world where like no one uses Ethereum,
but the Ethereum virtual machine lives
on. Monad uses EVM. It doesn't have any
connection with the Ethereum layer 1,
but it has seemingly very good technical
uh attributes.
Uh so you could and BNB chain uses CVM,
right? Again, no direct connection to
Ethereum. So I think we we kind of need
to be honest about that and like
acknowledge it. Sometimes it's being
dismissed as just FUD. I think there are
like two questions with Ethereum. One is
does the L2 model actually work? Is that
like successful? Can you, you know, have
L2s that are used a lot? I think B is
probably one of the top examples that
yes, it can work.
>> Uh that's question number one. And
question number two is are we going to
have scaling at the L1 layer?
>> We've been asking that question for a
long time. Yeah,
>> to me now at this point it's kind of
feels a bit like you kind of just had to
commit to the L2 road map. You know,
it's like
>> in a world with all of these different
chains, the L2 one is at least somewhat
differentiated, right? Maybe the like
the closest comparison would be
something like Avalanche L1s,
you know, that are kind of EVM chains
potentially. I think you can choose, but
then they are not really L2s. their own
L1s that use the avalanche framework,
right? So anyway, I think like I'm a big
believer in a multi-chain future. We're
in a multi-chain present now for sure
and I think the future is also
multi-chain, but different chains will
play different roles just like different
operating systems like Linux, Windows,
you know, OSX, whatever.
>> Jack Mers was on the show and he said
something I still remember till this
day. He said being useful like having
utility doesn't equal something's going
to go up. For example, you are not going
to store US dollar, it's very useful to
increase your asset because it is not an
appreciating asset.
>> Yeah.
>> In this case,
>> even if Ethereum is super useful and
contributes to a lot of things, that
doesn't necessarily mean I should invest
in it.
>> Yeah, I think that's accurate.
>> Like people are saying it's not going to
go away. I think we all acknowledge that
already, but it's just people are
asking, should we invest in it?
>> Yeah. Well, you you can distinguish
between Ethereum, the chain,
EVM, the technology or framework,
whatever,
>> and then ETH, the asset. So, it's
perfectly possible to be bullish on like
one or more of those, but not all.
Right. Right.
>> Right. And like
>> uh you could be bullish on Ethereum. I I
think in theory you could be quite
bullish on Ethereum as the chain and EVM
but not ETH the asset maybe.
>> Of course, you know, people would get
would get into the weeds and say, well,
if people use Ethereum L1 a lot, that's
going to burn a lot of ETH and you know,
all these different things. But I don't
know. I think it's important not to
conflate the different things and be
hygienic in how we think about these
concepts. I heard this theory about if
everything's going on chain and the US
wants to be the capital crypto capital
of the world then they should come up
with the USA chain.
>> That's Salana, right?
>> No. [laughter] Um
>> is it
>> Salana obviously is a global chain but
it has a really strong presence in the
US. Um but so does like Avalanche for
example.
>> Um
>> so we're not talking about a whole new
chain. I met with some people in Tokyo
who are building Japan smart chain
>> and that's kind of their vision, right?
To to have domestic validators of the
chain cuz I asked them like hey we could
be a validator for Japan smart chain
like actually we want Japanese companies
to be validators and so yeah could make
sense maybe. I think do you have like
domestic internets? I guess you could
argue maybe China has its own domestic
internet to some extent,
>> but I think generally blockchains are
more useful when they're global.
>> One question about your new product that
is AI driven. You were talking about
that you can ask AI a problem and
basically they give you suggestions or
references.
>> Yeah.
>> But a lot of products are doing that
now.
>> How how is yours different?
>> Yeah, totally. So number one, we care
about quality. So just for context, we
are probably the best company in the
world at labeling addresses. Okay.
>> And we have 500 million addresses
labeled.
>> Wow.
>> And every label we have evidence so that
if you ask me, hey, why is this labeled
Arthur Hayes?
>> Yeah. Why?
>> I can look at in the database and I can
figure out
>> about it. because he mentioned it here
or like he posted a link there. He he
was active on the governance forum
there. Like there's always a piece of
evidence for every one of those 500
million levels. So quality assurance is
kind of baked into our DNA. And so we
take that same both technical knowhow of
doing agentic attribution labeling of
addresses and quality assurance and
we're now using that for agentic
interactions
>> surrounding onchain. So we run evals
which is kind of kind of sort of AI
speak for I guess quality assurance or
evaluation um of how the agent is doing.
So we we basically measure if we make
changes to our agent does it hallucinate
more like if it can make up stuff like
oh yeah cuz you could go to in theory
you could go to one of the other ones or
one of these like not so good products
in crypto and it just like makes
something up. It's like here's a token
and literally it can make up the symbol.
It can make up some some stats.
>> So we really
religiously measure to what extent does
it hallucinate and then you of course
minimize the amount of hallucination and
you don't release it unless it's like
above a certain threshold
>> in its ability to not hallucinate.
>> Um another example is if you have
certain prompts that are execution
focused like buy $10 worth of Pangu.
Does it manage to translate that to the
actual order, the right token, the right
amount, you know, buy not sell, all this
stuff. We measure that, right? We
measure how good is the formatting of
the output. Is it actually concise and
clear or is it like way too long and
convoluted? And
>> and so we have a bunch of these
different um internal metrics that we
use to measure uh the quality of the
agent and make sure it's really really
good. And then we also measure in the
mobile app you can like thumbs up or
thumbs down the response. So we measure
like how much people actually like the
answer. Not that's not enough but you do
that as well. And our basically score
there is 95% right of of the the
answers. So people generally really like
the responses. So I'd say like the first
overall area is just quality which
relates to trust because what is
inevitably going to happen next year is
you're going to have tons of a aentic
trading products and I think most of
them are going to do some like
horrendous mistakes that are going to
lose a lot of people money and they're
going to blow up and go out of business,
right? And our approach is like let's
make sure that does not happen because
we care about our users and we want to
make sure that they can preserve and
grow their portfolios. We can't
guarantee it but we can do our very best
to make sure that nothing bad happens.
So I think like quality trust are super
important and then I think the other
part is generally people know the
nonsense brand. They know that we can be
trusted for analytics, for data. And so
I think we have a little bit of brand
asset that we can use there for trading
as well. We're a serious company that's
here for the long run. Hopefully I'll
build this company until I die, right?
And who knows, maybe my my daughter
takes over the the company or something,
but it's not like a single cycle
company. We're here for the long run.
That's how I would think about it. Just
better quality. People can try it
themselves. We run tons of evals
internally. What I would love to do is
to create benchmarks that we can run all
the other agentic products against
>> and see who's actually best just like we
do with Claude, you know, OpenAI models,
Gemini. We should have benchmarks like
that and then we can actually
objectively measure that Nunson is
indeed the best agentic trading problem.
>> Before I let you go, you said you have a
daughter.
>> Yeah. So for everyone that's watching,
what should a kid really learn nowadays
because the world is very very
uncertain?
>> Sounds like we're heading into something
really cool but unsure.
>> Yeah, I mean I don't have a great
answer. I think uh for parents I would
recommend the book The Anxious
Generation which talks about uh uh
smartphone usage and social media and
how it has negatively impacted a lot of
young people. that means you probably
shouldn't be uh exposing your kids to
smartphones and social media at a very
young age and then maybe reflect a bit
on how AI relates to that. I think AI
obviously has tremendous potential for
good in education and so on, but I think
we shouldn't just like let our kids run
around with like AI smartwatches that
they can talk to 24/7 which I know is
getting common someplace. My view is
like a bit of a barbell approach where
you kind of have two extremes. One is
totally organic, no smart devices, no
screens out in the woods or playing
football or touching grass.
>> And then the other one like super
frontier in engage with the latest
technology, learn to use AI uh and then
do both but like have a healthy balance.
>> That was a beautiful conversation. I
appreciate your time and please come
back soon. Yeah, happened.